Maomao's Diaries
I'm exhausted again today.
Even though I'm back in the Pleasure District,
trouble keeps finding its way to me...
Freckles!
Hey, Chou!
Is something wrong?
You know,
you really should be nicer to people!
What's with this brat, coming out of nowhere with that?
You were bullying that old guy earlier,
weren't you?!
Huh? When did I ever do that?
You were shoving a huge pile of grasshoppers into his mouth!
I was not!
Rokushoukan = Verdigris House
Even the big sisters of the Rokushoukan looked disgusted!
There are people who really can't stand them, you know!
I don't think doing stuff like that is right!
Like I said, I wasn't bullying him. That was...
Ah, right.
I was just making him take his medicine.
Time for Maomao's Trivia!
Since ancient times, grasshoppers
have been used as an ingredient in crude herbal medicine.
They are said to be effective for relieving coughs and reducing fever.
He said his cough was terrible,
so I just prescribed a slightly larger dose.
Oh, is that what it was?
Good thing he's an idiot kid.
By the way, who was that old guy anyway?
Didn't it seem like he was trying to talk to me at first?
It's just your imagination.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone around here is nothing but trouble.
Next time:
Robe of the Fire Rat
To be continued